{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/1029","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1029","name":"New Paradigm/Glazer Elementary","address":"2001 LaBelle","zipcode":"48238","owner":"Keys Grace Academy","licenseNumber":"243140","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.11761,42.39878","geojson":{"id":"1029","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.11760976,42.398782978]},"properties":{"name":"New Paradigm/Glazer Elementary","owner":"Keys Grace Academy","address":"2001 LaBelle","zipcode":"48238","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"243140","establishmentid":"1029","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2022-04-19"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1306","name":"Detroit Collegiate Prep. High School","address":"2200 Grand Blvd. W.","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"3502","name":"Joy Preparatory Academy - Oakman Campus","address":"1129 Oakman Blvd.","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"2662","name":"Robinson Dairy Vending","address":"1200 Oakman","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"2942","name":"Corporate Dining Services","address":"1200  Oakman","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"1846","name":"ROMAN VENDING CO","address":"1200 OAKMAN","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"1327","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken W812114","address":"1695 Grand Blvd. E.","zipcode":"48211"},{"establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","address":"13331 Fourteenth","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"51623749","name":"Supreme Black Belt LLC","address":"13331 Fourteenth","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"4602","name":"Modern Vending","address":"1360 Oakman Blvd.","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"2582","name":"Detroit City High School","address":"13141 Rosa Parks","zipcode":"48238"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61476","inspectionDate":"2022-10-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"60029","inspectionDate":"2022-07-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"57512","inspectionDate":"2022-03-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"55420","inspectionDate":"2021-07-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53571","inspectionDate":"2020-12-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53198","inspectionDate":"2020-10-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51924","inspectionDate":"2020-06-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51279","inspectionDate":"2020-03-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49473","inspectionDate":"2019-10-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"47648","inspectionDate":"2019-05-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"44279","inspectionDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-11-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"42312","inspectionDate":"2018-05-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40397","inspectionDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Cooking equipment","subItem":"oven","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"MICROWAVE","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Hand-drying towels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"3-202.15","violationDescription":"FOOD packages shall be in good condition and protect the integrity of the contents so that the FOOD is not exposed to ADULTERATION or potential contaminants. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food package(s)","subItem":"Cans","problemDescription":"Dented, dented on seam or swollen","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Dented can(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]},{"inspectionid":"39042","inspectionDate":"2017-06-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment can openers","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36990","inspectionDate":"2016-10-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1029"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}